<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Permanent Proxy</string>
    <!--
    This string is used for square devices and overridden by hello_world in
    values-round/strings.xml for round devices.
    -->
    <string name="hello_world">Hello Square World!</string>
    <string name="start_proxy">Start Proxy</string>
    <string name="adb_enabled">Please enable ADB over bluetooth and \"always allow computer\" if asked.</string>
    <string name="success_proxy">Successfully set proxy</string>
    <string name="status">Proxy:</string>
    <string name="loading">loading…</string>
    <string name="proxy">Proxy</string>
    <string name="start_on_boot">Enable on boot</string>
    <string name="set_proxy">Set proxy</string>
    <string name="set_proxy_address">Set proxy address</string>
    <string name="set_proxy_port">Set proxy port</string>
    <string name="not_enabled">Proxy not enabled</string>
    <string name="something_wrong">Something went wrong, try again</string>
    <string name="show_me_how">How to enable ADB over Bluetooth?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_enable_adbbluetooth">EnableADBBluetoothActivity</string>
    <string name="instructions"><![CDATA[To get started, first enable the Developer Options of your watch, which can be achieved by going to Settings -> System -> About and tap the Build number until you are a \"developer\".\nNext, go to Settings -> Developer options and enable \"ADB debugging\" and \"Debug over Bluetooth\".\nFinally start up Permanent Proxy, request permission and press \"Allow\" or \"Always allow this Computer\" if prompted.\nAfter the app has gotten permission, ADB can be turned off again unless you want to disable the proxy.\n\nNow you can get started! Simply enter a proxy address and port, enable it (and on boot if you like) and you\'re done!\n\nProxy services can be found online and can be from any country. However, do make sure you completely trust the proxy you chose before you enter it! All the data of your watch might be sent through that proxy, even sensitive data, so act at your own risk.]]></string>
    <string name="requesting_permission">Requesting permission, this can take a while… \"Allow\" or \"Always allow computer\" if prompted.\nNote: the app works best with WiFi turned OFF.</string>
    <string name="wss_permission_needed">Write secure settings permission needed. This can be enabled via ADB over Bluetooth.</string>
    <string name="request_permission">ADB over Bluetooth is enabled, request permission!</string>
    <string name="permission_granted">Permission granted, ADB can be turned off unless you want to disable the proxy.</string>
    <string name="enable_proxy">Enable proxy</string>
    <string name="disable_proxy">Disable proxy (ADB needed, will reboot watch)</string>
    <string name="turning_off">Turning off proxy, please wait…</string>
    <string name="current_ext">External IP:</string>
    <string name="NA">N/A</string>
    <string name="other_apps">Other apps and external IP might take time to update.</string>
</resources>
